(Leonard:)How does your brain feel about
calculating the surface tension
(Leonard:)of the domain walls?
(Sheldon:)Let's see.
(begins tune)
Hey! I was humming.
(Sheldon:)One point
for Hufflepuff.
(repeats tune)
(Sheldon:)What song is that?
(Leonard:)Well... Hum it again.
(repeats tune)
Is that the SpongeBob song?
(to same tune): ♪ Who lives
in a pineapple ♪ Nope.
(Leonard:)Whatever. Can we just
get back to this?
(Sheldon:)I feel like I know
what song that is,
(Sheldon:)but I can't put
my finger on it.
♪ My country, 'tis of thee ♪
No.
(Leonard:)It's just an earworm.
It'll come to you.
(Sheldon:)Okay.
♪ R-E-S-P-E-C-T ♪
(Sheldon:)No.
(Leonard:)Is this what we're doing
the rest of the night?
♪ I'm surprised
you have to ask... ♪
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪